Alex NP I-PER
is NP O
going NV O
to NP O
Los NP I-LOC
Angeles NP I-LOC
in NP O
California NP I-LOC

Tom NP I-PER
is NP O
going NV O
to NP O
New NP I-LOC
York NP I-LOC
in NP O
Tokyo NP I-LOC

Sara NP I-PER
went NV O
to NP O
Saitama NP I-LOC
in NP O
Kanto NP I-LOC
